[Music]
in life we all have to make choices
whether it is to chase our dreams or to
find a great place to eat sometimes the
need to make a choice happens all too
suddenly and we have to make sure it's
the right one when you choose ICICI
Lombard you lay your worries down
whether you have a two-wheeler or
four-wheeler we have your vehicle
insured we are with you through
difficult times and situations till the
end you can take your vehicle to any
garage of your choice for repair for a
hassle-free experience we recommend you
to take your vehicle to one of our
partner garages for a cashless
settlement with cashless claim you don't
have to worry about the repair payment
the repair expenses are paid directly to
the partner garage you only need to pay
for the expenses not covered as an added
benefit of choosing our partner garage
the rest of of the process of the claim
will be taken care of by us the
advantages don't stop here you also get
a 6-month guarantee on all repairs for
your ease there are multiple ways to let
us know about this incident you can
choose to intimate us through our app
the IL takecare app will take care of
your motor claim process starting from
reporting a claim tracking progress all
the way till the settlement of your
claim tap on claims in the homepage
select the motor policy and tap on
report a
claim download the app now for a
seamless
experience you can also call us on our
toll-free number 1 18
02666 and follow simple ivr instructions
to get your claim registered another
easy way to claim your motor insurance
is through WhatsApp simply send a hi to
us in the number provided and choose the
right options once your claim number is
is generated you can start tracking your
claim status on our IL takecare app or
through WhatsApp so you have intimated
the claim in The Next Step a claim
manager is assigned to you you can now
immediately upload the supporting
documents on IL takecare app you can
also upload the documents via WhatsApp
or share it with your claim manager
after the documents are uploaded the
inspection process begins the claim
manager can assign a surveyor to inspect
your car
but as customer ease is always the top
priority at IC Lombard we have
eliminated the need for a physical
survey with il takecare apps instas
spect through instas spect you can get
an instant inspection of your vehicle
via a video call with your surveyor the
surveyor examines your vehicle to assess
the extent of the damages while also
getting your documents verified in this
process instas spects outcome is instant
approval
once the vehicle reaches the garage the
repair begins as the vehicle is being
repaired you can track the claim on IL
takecare app or Whatsapp once the repair
is completed you will immediately
receive an SMS on your registered mobile
number the garage will then send the
repair Bill to the claim manager your
claim manager adds the deductions to the
repair Bill and calculates the final
amount your claim amount is then
finalized if you have chose on one of
our partner garages the payment process
is cashless you will only have to pay
for the expense not covered in your
policy for non-partner garages you pay
the full amount at the garage and get
the amount
reimbursed once the final bill is
cleared the vehicle is back in your
hands make your journey happy and safe
and your claims fully hasslefree with
ICC
Lombard